Ilsa's back! ...More fierce than ever! With brutal fury she
enslaved an empire and shocked the world!
Ilsa: Harem Keeper of the Oil Sheiks is a action,
horror, war film directed by Don Edmonds.
Ilsa works for an Arab sheik who enjoys importing females to use as sex slaves.
Ilsa, played by Dyanne Thorne.
Commander Adam Scott, played by Max Thayer.
El Sharif, played by Jerry Delony.
Inga Lindström, played by Uschi Digard.
Nora Edward, played by Colleen Brennan.
Belly Dancer, played by Haji.
Ilsa, Harem Keeper of the Oil Sheiks is a 1976 sexploitation women in
prison film, the first sequel to Ilsa, She Wolf of the SS.
The film was directed by Don Edmonds.
The tone is dark and intense.